Rock [\h__\h] you shaking ass with they
hand out.
>> [music]
>> Yeah, rock [\h__\h] ass with they hand out.
Yeah, rock [\h__\h] you shaking ass with
>> [music]
>> If you ain't getting money ain't no rain
out. Rock [\h__\h] you shaking ass with
they hand
>> [music]
[music]
>> I really need somebody. Tell me you got
somebody.
I don't care about your body. [music]
Uh.
Love the way you touch my body.
Turn around and eat that body. I never
tell [music] no
I need you boy, all I need is you.
>> [music]
>> It's just me and you boy, it's just me
and you. I really need somebody.
Tell me you got somebody.
>> Baby, tell me what [music] you in the
mood for. Type [\h__\h] we should get a room
for. Got me in a mirror getting cute
for. Lay back, let me show you [music]
what I do for. Pull out the bad lady and
a new toy. Blow back, now we kissing in
the food court. You the type that I
would have skipped [music] school for.
Hell, this [\h__\h] I got you on my mood
board. I want to live in your skin.
When I jump out, you [music] jump in. I
see I diss in my plans. Same way I
picture you in my plans. Love a bad
[\h__\h] we just [music] friends. But I
hate that we just friends. Round two, he
want a [\h__\h] over it over again and
again. Can't
>> [music]
>> I really need somebody.
Tell me you got somebody. I don't care
about your body.
>> [music]
>> Uh.
Love the way you touch my body.
>> We finna put our clothes on.
I'mma show y'all what we wearing. We got
this, but it say video vixen on it. This
skirt. Also from Shein.
To go with this.
Cute. We putting on a Kurt bag and some
black heels, of course. We going to be
taking pictures. I'm putting on this and
this perfume. And I had got some body
oil to put on our legs, you know,
glistening, looking good, smelling good,
feeling good, okay? But yeah, when I
come back, we going to be in our
clothes.
>> [snorts]
>> Y'all, it is 2:42. We just now done with
all our videos and stuff. And yeah.
Y'all, we made it.
>> It's going to take us a couple shots.
>> And hey, inside See what they talking
about? It's a lot of people here, but
it's also a lot of people leaving. They
over here charging 60, 80, and 100 for
parking.
Got that [\h__\h] for 25.
>> Definitely got it for 25.
>> Ooh.
Damn
I can smell it already.
All right.
I'll bet you get ready.
How many shots you going to take?
>> [\h__\h] two.
>> Cheers to 34K and my girl being
consistent on YouTube.
>> Mhm. Cheers to new beginnings.
>> Yep. Yep.
>> I don't know what's worse.
The liquor or the warm chaser.
>> That [\h__\h] so nasty.
>> Let's take one more.
It depend on what we feeling like.
>> This [\h__\h] just nasty as [\h__\h]
>> I did.
>> Oh my god.
>> We all have fun there.
>> [music]
>> Yeah, body heat.
Body heat.
You almost there.
He thought about tiger.
>> [laughter]
>> Mhm?
Cute.
I'm so I'm not even like overly drunk,
but
>> I'm feeling good. Like it ain't nothing.
Wait.
I'm just
>> It's about that time. I'm so hot.
Drunk ain't even a word.
>> Right, I'm feeling good. I ain't even
hot.
>> Yes, I feel good. We definitely what?
Somebody had gave us a shot. We did not
take that [\h__\h]
Did not take them [\h__\h] I'm cool.
Thank you. Look at my lips. I know I
think they look good cuz I fixed them.
But I'm sweating.
Damn, her storage full.
We going to come back when we in the
car.
Woo!
Look at me. I'm sweating, sweating.
Anyway, y'all, it's us after the club.
Yeah, we feeling good or whatever. We is
hot.
>> Time for me to start a business. She
love [music] me, she ain't hurt by me
since then.
>> I had to make sure the door was locked.
Continue.
>> [music]
>> Just pull [music] up on the LA.
>> Bro, this is all my [\h__\h] head.
We are here to ball.
>> [music]
>> That's your truth.
[music]
>> Huh?
>> Y'all must be from out of state, right?
>> I am.
>> Damn, what's up? What's up? Where where
is the party at?
>> I can
>> This is LIKE THE PARTY.
>> HELL NO.
>> MEET ME AT THE MOVE.
>> Good move.
>> That's what I heard.
>> You want to All right, we'll see.
>> You want to get up no more, right?
>> We'll see.
We live here.
>> We'll see what they're talking about.
>> is about.
>> Both of y'all are beautiful, you know. I
don't
>> Thank [clears throat] you.
>> Thank you.
She is fine, though. You are You are
fine, too. I ain't going to hit on both
of y'all, though.
>> You are.
NOW YOU GETTING WHY DON'T you say what
if you one of my friends? I'm cool.
Thank you.
>> In front of our faces.
>> It's okay.
>> You got to work on that. Americans
>> Americans don't do that.
>> Yeah, we don't do that.
>> If anything, hide it.
>> If anything
>> They hide it.
>> You think about it, but you don't say
it.
>> don't say that.
>> Now you just offended both of us.
>> You know, I don't want nobody to feel
bad, you know. So, what if I can have
two instead of one?
>> No, not two. This ain't that type of
party.
>> Yeah, we're friends.
>> Friends do everything together.
>> Not that.
>> For the party.
>> go there. We'll meet you there.
>> Y'all ain't going to give me that. Well,
nice to meet y'all. I'm Tony, by the
way. I ain't going to see y'all no more,
right?
>> It's 6 minutes. WE GOING TO GO.
>> RIGHT.
>> WE GOING TO MEET YOU
>> WE GOING TO MEET YOU THERE.
>> OKAY. OKAY. WE GOING TO MEET you there.
Okay.
>> Bye.
>> We'll see you later.
>> Bye, Tony. See you.
>> And Liz, um
Great.
Bro, he just sobered me up real quick.
>> For real, like I really had a
>> Bye, Tony. Look at Tony, y'all.
>> I think Tony about to walk in.
>> Tony finna go in No, he going in that
truck right there.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> See Beth home so we could be safe.
>> We over here dancing. I
see a black cigarette.
>> Yes.
>> Oh, look, it's Tony.
Tony need to relax. He need to
>> No, for real. Tony need to Tony need to
like
>> You
>> Dude, he look too bald. Maybe that's the
Bahamas or whatever, but he talking
about what if I wanted you? Why you pass
me to her?
>> For real.
>> What make you think you could get me
after that? You couldn't get me before
that. What What make you think you could
get me after that? Then you going to
proceed to say, "What if I could have
had both OF Y'ALL?"
>> WOO!
CAN. LIKE
>> YOU CAN HAVE NEITHER.
>> This is not that type of party.
>> The hell?
What the hellion? What the hellion out
there?
>> [laughter]
>> WHAT THE HELLION?
NO, for real.
>> But My what's the word?
>> bucked up beyond [\h__\h] up.
>> Maybe in the Bahamas, but here?
It's been a successful night.
We took a couple shots. We did not get
too lit.
Now we on the way back home. It is 5:54
in the morning. We went from spot to
spot.
>> It was a cool night.
What do you guys say?
>> Um yeah, night was cool or whatever. I'm
hungry, trying to go get me some food,
and my mouth is dry.
Um yeah, and I can't wait to do it all
over tomorrow. Yeah.
>> Yeah, thank you.
>> Y'all, it's 6:43, and we just came to
Wendy's because I wanted something.
So I got me a sandwich. It's a honey I
don't know. I seen honey and chicken and
biscuit.
>> I think it had gravy in it, too.
>> Honey biscuit
honey
biscuit and
>> chicken they got me.
Definitely got me. Definitely took my
little $3.50.
And now we waiting on them.
Yeah.
>> I like that sleep just like punched me
in the face right now.
>> Now that you staying still.
>> Yeah. Like I was on go. Like I was on
>> We had a cool little night though.
Y'all we left out overly late. Like
>> We like oh yeah we going to get out like
6:00, 7:00.
>> Yes. 6:00, 7:00.
>> We was like oh yeah we just got a little
maintenance to do. Not that much.
>> Yes.
>> Ended up leaving the house 2:00, 3:00.
It's just
>> It's cool though.
>> We was supposed to do so much but we
still got to do it. It don't matter.
>> Yeah this only the first day.
>> Eyes watering.
Can't wait to take my makeup off.
>> Yes.
I can't wait to eat.
>> Lay my ass down.
>> Wrap my hair, put my pajamas on.
I'm
going to sleep good. We got some things
to do today.
Y'all going to see though. They was on
our body per usual.
I'm up can't even sleep. [\h__\h] I'm up.
[\h__\h] I'm geeked.
When I'm in your city got to make me
turn up.
Yeah.
>> We the only ones
>> at least I'm it's fresh.
>> They taking forever though.
>> It's hot and ready. They on our body.
Stop. Thank you.
>> I think your baby crazy. Just here
honey. The lunch.
>> Bag secured.
>> [music]
>> Yeah.
>> To make the crust then.
>> Oh.
>> [music]
>> Yeah.
[music]
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> We had a good first day.
Yeah. So, it's 6:14.
And
I really miss sleep all day, but we're
not doing nothing. We finna go get some
some food, and we finna get some
cut water.
>> Cut. Cut. Cut. Cut. Cut. Cut.
>> Last Friday night, you had me doing some
table tops. They had me wilding out. I
forgot.
Last Friday night.
I don't know the lyrics.
Do it all
again.
That's Friday night. We is going to do
it all over again. Well, not all of it.
Somebody having a party, so we might see
what's hitting on. I had ended up
messing up my toes
in the club. Sorry, I got to fix them.
But, we should be out earlier today
because we ain't got nothing to do. Even
though it's 6:00, we just going with the
flow. That's our only plan for tonight,
so we was supposed to get up early, but
we was tired. We didn't do something we
had plans to do, but we going to do it
tomorrow.
Y'all, we going to get some Chipotle.
Then, we going to get some cold water.
Yeah. Y'all, YouTube gave me some
Chipotle.
That's why I'm here.
So, shout out to them, y'all.
>> [snorts]
>> They be having these heavy, though.
You got to overthrow your body.
It used to smell like the Chipotle
smelling how it used to smell.
Get that. We ain't got no money.
Somebody said that the [\h__\h]
tables are dirty.
They They ain't cleaning up, bro.
Grubhub extra for double. They be
skipping. Nah, give me double.
Give me more rice. I need that.
>> I need all that.
>> Uh-huh.
Y'all, we got the The in the backseat.
>> Where yours at?
>> On the floor.
>> Oh, her kid on the floor. Neglect.
Neglect. She neglecting her kid.
But now, we finna go try to find these.
Y'all, yesterday we was looking for the
cut waters. We could not find them or
like the flavor we wanted. So, we finna
go look. It's 7:13. We do still want a
smoothie, too. We going to go inside um
after we done [clears throat]
looking for our stuff. Well, if we find
it. Well, we going to find it. But, we
going to go inside
and eat, then start getting ready, and
head to this party and see what the
party talking about. Depending on how it
is, we going to see. We might go to a
spot, I don't know. When it come to
night time, we go with the flow. During
the daytime, we'll have some plans. But,
today we had plans, but we was tired. We
came in the house late.
>> So, early.
>> Yeah, we came in the house.
>> 6:00 a.m. 6:30.
>> Yes.
We got sidetracked and now we're going
to TJ Maxx. Y'all, I told him my name
Bree. He put Bree. I spelled it out and
everything, and he put Bree. But, it's
okay.
Ooh, Bree might be my name tonight.
Bree.
They Halloween down already.
It's cute, though.
Yeah, we going to do some pink. We going
to have us a little spooky little spooky
girls night.
Y'all, we got the effort out of Lulu.
>> Yeah, Lulu ain't had none.
>> We wasn't hitting on nothing. So,
we finna go grab these last couple
things, head in the house,
eat, and start getting ready. And we
going to see what we get into tonight.
I love the summer. Y'all, before I did
not care for the summer like But, now
that I'm like grown,
maybe the summer not bad. Like, maybe I
see the hype.
I understand.
It's 9:17. We back inside, finally.
Y'all, I just took a real quick shower
because Mari trying to be somewhere,
right? And basically she got her timing
wrong, so I didn't even have to do that.
But it's okay cuz I got time to eat and
I could do my makeup, too. So, it's
okay.
>> You forgive me?
>> Yeah.
I do. It's no biggie.
I got I could eat my food like I thought
I was going to have to rush eat my food
and stuff. But yeah, so I'm going to
just come back when we getting ready cuz
I threw my pajamas so them back.
>> home in the meantime.
>> Stop doing this to
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, [\h__\h]
>> [music]
>> We going to scare the hoes away.
All right, Shau, we made it to the
party. Cut the [\h__\h] cameras.
Y'all, why somebody just decided to
start popping some fireworks? I don't
play that [\h__\h] and
Okay, my shorts coming up.
I'm so mad I dropped my straw.
>> where you at.
>> I'm almost done.
>> I need y'all vlog.
>> Huh?
>> Yeah. What's your name?
>> Ria.
>> Ria? What's your name?
>> Mari.
>> Y'all got YouTube?
>> I do.
>> Yeah, she do.
>> I do streaming.
>> Girl.
>> Excuse me.
>> Say hi to my friend YouTube.
>> 28 days.
>> We got shot in
>> [laughter]
>> This [\h__\h] turned the [\h__\h] Oh.
SHE OPENED THIS LIKE 2 HOURS AGO. WHY IS
IT STILL FULL?
>> When you get me on my knees, [music]
boy, you give me shivers. When we make
love, you hear me screaming like a
rebel.
>> [music]
[music]
>> We definitely be all night.
>> What happened at the new
>> What a night, y'all. What a night.
This what we doing.
You know what I'm saying? That's why you
got
That's why you supposed to get you some
food before you go outside. It's going
to come in handy.
This did not taste this good earlier.
>> Y'all, I was going to eat one of them.
It's just as well.
>> Hm?
I'm going to come back to mine well
later on today.
So, we on a tour a house tour right now.
Look at her.
She is Look at the view.
And it's a lot of space.
It's the big
Wait, what is this? Oh, this is the like
the laundry and stuff.
I could get lost up in here.
>> [laughter]
>> Here, it's really nice.
Oh, okay. Let me show y'all the
bathroom.
Look at the shower. This is the shower,
y'all.
Wait.
That big old closet.
Ooh, I can't wait.
Yeah, I'm putting that manifest to start
now. But this is so bad. This a big old
closet. Like you just imagine.
You could yes, and still have room to
walk around. Like this is a whole
separate this another room.
This not even a closet. This is a room.
First of all, it already look good.
Imagine this decorated. What?
What? Bro, it's just this for me. I
really just like the
this this big old mirror, too.
And it's a view, too. Like you just see
a little lake and stuff.
All right, y'all. This is the second
property that we're looking at.
She not going to like this. [laughter]
All right, y'all. We better
We got to go upstairs, see what upstairs
hitting on. Downstairs not really
hitting on nothing, but here's like a
bonus area. Um
it's carpet throughout.
Yeah, she not going to like this. I just
know she not going to like this. She
in the closet. I feel like the other one
The other one was way better. We like
the
Okay, they got like a storage.
The floors don't match the cabinets,
though. Yeah, they lost me. The
bathrooms, but I do like the mirror.
The outlet in the mirror, that's cool.
This part pissed me off. Why would you
build like this?
Do it at least.
But why would you need two doors? Why
don't you just
take this out and then have a
>> Oh, it's like a fake wall. Like you
could walk in it.
>> [\h__\h] [laughter]
Then it's like these small windows.
like, it's giving prison.
>> [laughter]
>> Giving inmate.
You won't let me out.
>> No, that other one, yeah.
>> Yeah, that one set the tone. This one is
cool for the right person.
>> Yeah.
>> We not the right people.
>> And it it's for like a little somebody a
little older.
>> Yeah.
>> See, it's nice though.
>> It is.
>> We done with that one. Y'all, it is so
hot.
>> And Texas is like
>> I'm mad I got a long sleeve on. And it's
only 88, it feel like a 100. They making
sure they sell and build these houses
ASAP, no rocky.
I see. I see it.
This I like the the windows.
But it's the floors, the floors give
basement.
Yeah.
Just the washer. Oh, this is a big room.
You know, we like a closet.
>> Yeah,
I do.
>> It's cool.
>> It is.
Is it the other one?
>> It ain't topping that one. Nothing
topping that.
>> like we should have seen that one last.
>> Yes.
Now, okay, the bathroom.
Ooh, private toilets.
We love that.
>> I do.
I love the mirror again.
>> The outlet in the mirror, nice little
closet.
I like the colorway though.
>> Yeah.
>> Even the carpet, like the carpet is not,
you know.
>> Yeah.
It's pretty weird.
>> Mhm.
>> Is there a walk-in closet?
>> No, you could walk in there though.
>> We getting started boys, but you better
hide your
>> [music]
[music]
>> [\h__\h] yeah we YouTubing. We in Houston
trying to turn up in the night.
Okay. [singing]
Okay.
This the wagster. [music]
If that [\h__\h] ain't got a APC it's not
mad.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Y'all, we tapping back in.
>> Let me turn the music off before you get
copyrighted. But, we had us a time. The
thing about it is we going to find us
some [\h__\h] to get into. We went out with
no plans. Everything paid for. We not
even in no crazy [\h__\h] She got two
and I got Under Armour on. We not even
dressed crazy.
>> G fazos, like nothing.
I done broke some nails.
>> For real. Whole night paid for.
>> I feel like I'm losing my voice. How you
feeling?
>> I'm feeling cool. I'm hungry. Stomach
touching my ass.
>> We about to go in the house and we about
to
recover. And hopefully we will have some
tonight for y'all like a
Love Island type night. Chilling.
>> Yeah.
>> Cuz after tonight
we had some cut water.
>> Yeah.
>> We had some Patron.
>> I smoked.
>> We overdid it a little bit. But we was
cool.
>> Yeah, we was cool.
>> We still know our limits.
>> Don't tell me and my good sis, all
right?
>> And yeah, so well today we going to be
on some cool stuff today. We didn't did
our clubbing and all that. We want to
keep it cute later on today. Damn,
I'm so hungry, y'all. It's 6:59.
Houston don't sleep.
I can only imagine Miami. We got to hit
up Miami. Good morning.
It's breakfast.
Lunch regular time, but
we had a ball.
Come and find that [\h__\h] on me, baby.
[music]
We watching for boobs. I got my PANTS
TIGHT AS [\h__\h] HE WATCHING THE BOOBS.
>> [music]
>> Y'ALL WATCHING me lose. Wait, watching
for the face into the side.
Guys, we're at Dollar Tree to grab some
little things cuz stop playing like
don't be dumb with your money, okay? We
know you having it. We know.
>> Ain't nobody too good
>> But maintain it.
Maintain it. Go to Dollar Tree.
They got some good stuff. It's a dollar.
We need some cups for our pina colada.
Yeah, that's a cool little cup. This is
more like a margarita cup. But we could
bro, it's all [music] What they going to
do? Beat us up?
>> Exactly. Y'all going to beat us up for
real?
>> Nope.
>> [laughter]
>> Why? I I really like that cup.
>> That's [snorts] not cute.
>> Yeah. We might just [music] go with
these.
>> Cuz we can It's how we decorate it. We
can put like a cherry
>> Bro, and it's our life.
>> Literally.
>> So, we going We doing these.
>> No.
>> Yeah. We got some umbrellas. Our friends
told me, "Nigga, shut up. It's shot
o'clock."
>> I keep banging on
them. Let me stop.
Bags secured.
>> Yes, we done with Dollar Tree. Now we
got to go to Walmart
and the grocery store.
We still don't really even know what we
cooking, but y'all going to see, bro.
Yeah, it don't even matter. you you know
we good for it, so.
Okay, y'all. If y'all don't know, I
don't know, I think I told y'all we
having a Love Island
We watching Love Island and we getting
into the Love Island vibe.
So,
should we get these? They kind of get
like fruity, though.
And then like, we got to find pajamas
too if we wearing this. We got LGBTQ.
>> Be who you are.
>> We got to
For your pride.
>> Yeah. We can do these. She's cute and we
already got this one. [music]
So, we going to get these.
Y'all, we are at Kroger and we about to
grab these groceries. It's 9:23. So, we
going to be up tonight. But, when are we
not up?
No, we not up like in the middle of the
day.
>> We up at night.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
[music and singing]
[singing and music]
>> Hey, y'all. We back from grocery
shopping and my body hurt really,
really, really bad. And yeah, the queen
just like the queen body just going
through it. And my friend, she such a
real one, y'all, that you know we was
supposed to be cooking and stuff. She's
just going to cook and she told me like
to go take a bubble bath. So, she came
back with this tray that go in the
bathtub, you know, and some stuff like
bath bombs, little bath salts. She gave
me a candle and stuff. She's downstairs
cooking and we still going to do our
little girls' night whatever. I'm just
soaking. But, when I'm done, I am going
to do the drinks. So, she just on the
food, I'm on the drinks. So, y'all not
going to be seeing the food being made,
but y'all going to see like the after of
the food and stuff. Like, you'll be all
right. So, we just going to unwind
basically, you know? Just going to wrap
up my hair. We going to play some music.
We going to play some like cool chill
music. Even though I don't really be
caring for that, but that's the vibe. We
going to set the mood.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Okay, y'all. So, while I was making the
pina coladas, my SD card got full. So,
yeah, it stopped recording while I was
making them. But, we're done with the
food and the pina coladas. So, I'm going
to show y'all the food back there as you
can see. Food looking too good. Y'all
I'm going to start up this hookah.
>> [music]
[music]
>> We got the hookah going. We got our
drinks. We got the cupcakes.
We got our food. And yeah.
Oh, it's 3:36
>> [laughter]
>> in the morning.
And what? Who going to do something
about it?
>> [music]
[singing]
>> Okay, y'all.
Yeah.
Ooh, this is hot.
I don't even know how to explain like
how this tastes. You know you want some,
too. Like, look at him.
Mhm.
Everything good, bro.
The sauce, the steak, the shrimp.
The best hell,
our pina colada tastes real good, too.
We got the section at home
with our matching pajamas on.
First of all, you see how we got
blankets? That's how you know like
we was getting a little too comfortable.
Y'all, how how far is is we into this?
We is
58 minutes into the first episode, and
we finna go lay down.
I don't know.
Maybe we got to pay attention next time.
Yeah, and the hookah, the food good,
too. The bro, good food make you sleepy.
But, we was already like setting ourself
up for failure. We supposed to been
making bracelets and stuff. We finna go
lay down.
We supposed to make Tik Toks and [\h__\h]
Who going to
Nobody.
Y'all, it's 12:39. I'm on my
>> [music]
>> I'm on my way home, but my body hurts so
bad. Like, in my next video, I think I
want to do like and I done broke some
nails outside. I think I want to do like
a I really want to go like to a spa. I
want to get like a massage or something.
to definitely need that. Like, my body,
she hurt. Lifting my arms, all this
hurt. Like, it's just sore. So, yeah.
But, that's really all I had to say
though. I can't wait to edit this video.
I'm finna be ending her off though.
Thank you so much for watching. Like,
comment, and subscribe for more, and
I'll be back next week with another
video, okay? Bye.